Juyong Jiang

🛘 +86 18761157121 🗷 csjuyongjiang@gmail.com 🆀 juyongjiang.work 🖸 juyongjiang 🖪 Blog

Education

Hohai University
 B.S in Computer Science and Technology
 GPA 88.76/100, 4.67/5.0, ranking top 8/107 in major

Nanjing, China *08/2016--07/2020*

Personal Profile

I received my Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and Technology, Hohai University with honors of the Excellent Bachelor Thesis Award and recommended as the Outstanding Bachelor Thesis in Jiangsu Province in July. 2020. I used to be a member of Hohai Mathematical Modeling Lab and then joined Hohai Al Development Group, under the supervision of Prof. Jianjun Ni. From Oct. 2019 till present, I am a Research Intern in IVA, NLPR, CASIA. My research interest are Computer Vision, NLP and GNN, with a focus on Object Detection, Instance Segmentation, GCN and Deep Learning, supervised by Prof. Jing Liu. So far, I have read more than 100 CVPR/ ICCV/ ECCV/ NIPS/ AAAI / ACL / EMNLP / NAACL papers so that I can understand and re-implement the new papers.

Publications

- Juyong Jiang, Jie Zhang and Kai Zhang. "Cascaded Semantic and Positional Self-Attention Network for Document Classification." In Proceedings of the Conference on Empirical Methods in Natural Language Processing (EMNLP), 2020. (Submit)
- Junfeng Chen, Juyong Jiang, et al. "A fault diagnosis system for rail transit platform doors based on deep learning." Chinese Patent. 201910613949.1.
- Jianjun Ni, Juyong Jiang, et al. "Bank card number positioning and recognition end-toend method based on CNN and RNN." Chinese Patent. 201910933476.3.
- Junfeng Chen, Juyong Jiang, et al. "Multi-regional precipitation prediction model construction method based on multi-graph convolution and memory network." Chinese Patent. 201911362437.9.

Projects

- Video & Image Instance Segmentation Based on Deep Learning. (03/2020--Present)
 - Predict both the location and the semantic mask of each instance in an image & video.
 - Add the module of ASPP, CoordConv, DCN, Global Pooling, Self-Attention, etc. on base-line framework to solve some problems and improve performance.
 - √ IVA, NLPR, CASIA & HuaWei.
- Spatiotemporal Attention Probes Mechanism (09/2019--02/2020)
 - Establish Spatiotemporal Graph.

- Use Query as a seed and then use the Markov Random Walk, Random Walk with Restart, Page Rank, etc. on Spatiotemporal Graph to form the interaction of neighborhood.
- Combine the node information in the neighborhood to generate polarity features.
- ✓ Temple University & Fudan University.
- Spatiotemporal Data Mining in Smart Cities Based on Deep Learning. (07/2019--08/2019)
 - Encode the non-Euclidean pair-wise correlations among regions into multiple graphs and then explicitly model these correlations using multi-graph convolution network.
 - Augments recurrent neural network with a contextual-aware gating mechanism to reweights different historical observations.
 - ✓ College of Computer Science and Technology, Zhejiang University.
- Bank Card Recognition System Based on Deep Learning. (03/2019--07/2019)
 - Data augmentation by using random cropping, rotation, various transformation, blur and noise.
 - Using CTPN & CRNN model to locate and recognize bank card number, respectively.
 - Developing a web page and an android app to display and use.
 - ✓ College of Internet of Things Engineering, Hohai University.

Experience

• Image & Video Analysis Group (IVA), National Laboratory of Beijing, China Pattern Recognition (NLPR), Institute of Automation, Chinese Academic of Sciences (CASIA)

Research Intern 10/2019--Present

- Worked on **instance segmentation** in images & videos with Dr. Xinjian He, supervised by Prof. **Jing Liu**.
- Department of Computer and Information Sciences, Temple Philadelphia, US
 University

Research Intern 08/2019--02/2020

- Worked on **natural language processing**, supervised by Prof. **Kai Zhang**.
- Pervasive Computing Lab (PCLab), College of Computer Science and Technology Zhejiang University

Research Intern 07/2019--08/2019

- Worked on **spatiotemporal data mining** in smart cities based on deep learning, supervised by Prof. **Ling Chen**.
- Al Development Group, College of Internet of Things Nanjing, China Enginee-ring, Hohai University

Research Assistant 08/2018--07/2020

- Worked on **application development** based on deep learning, supervised by Prof. **Jianjun Ni**.

Awards and Honors

- Bachelor Thesis is recommended as Outstanding Bachelor Thesis in Jiangsu Province (only 2 papers in Department of Information, Hohai University), 2020
- Excellent Bachelor Thesis Award in Hohai University (5%), 2020.
- Outstanding Student Honor in Hohai University, 2020.
- Outstanding Student Honor in Hohai University, 2019.
- Excellent Grades in Trash Classification Challenge Cup of Huawei Cloud Artificial Intelligence Contest, 2019.
- Top 10 Outstanding students, College of Internet of Things Engineering, Hohai University, 2018.
- Advanced Individual of Students at Social Practices in Summer Vacation. (Serve as Electronic Referee in The 19th Annual Games in Jiangsu Province), 2018.
- Research and Innovation Excellent Scholarship in Hohai University, 2020.
- Spirtiual Excellent Scholarship in Hohai University, 2020.
- Academic Excellent Scholarship in Hohai University, 2020.
- Spirtiual Excellent Scholarship in Hohai University, 2019.
- Academic Excellent Scholarship in Hohai University, 2019.
- National Encouragement Scholarship, 2018.
- Academic Excellent Scholarship in Hohai University, 2018.
- Academic Excellent Scholarship in Hohai University, 2017.

Mathematical Ability

- 2nd Prize for Certificate Authority Cup Mathematical Modeling Online Challenge (Second Stage), 2020.
- 2nd Prize for Certificate Authority Cup Mathematical Modeling Online Challenge (First Stage), 2020.
- Honorable Mention for Mathematical Contest in Modeling (MCM), 2018.
- Honorable Mention for Certificate Authority Cup International Mathematical Contest in Modeling (CAMCM), 2017.
- Excellent academic grades in all mathematic curriculum. (Advanced Mathematics-A, Linear Algebra-A, Probability and Statistics-A, Mathematical Modeling-A, Numerical Analysis and Computing-A, Discrete Mathematics-A, Data Structure and Algorithms-A)

Programming Skills

Language C / C++, Matlab, Java, Python

Web HTML / CSS, JavaScript, JSP, PHP

OS Linux

Framework Tensorflow, Pytorch